ARTUR OKHOTNICHENKO



Personal

- Phone number +358449254853
- Email ohotnikarturik@gmail.com
- Website https://artur-portfolio.netlify.app/
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/arturokhotnichenko-9104b9190/

Skills

UTM 666 6466

HTML, CSS, SASS	
MaterializeCSS, NativeBase	••••
JavaScript, TypeScript	••••
React.js, Next.js, Gatsby.js	••••
React Native, Expo	••••
Redux	••••
MERN	••••
Express.js, Node.js,	••••
MongoDB, Mongoose	••••
Jest	••••
AWS	••••
REST API, GraphQL	••••
Bash, CLI, Docker	
Git, GitHub, Netlify	••••
Contentful CMS	••••
WebStorm, Visual Studio	••••
Postman	••••
Photoshop, Figma, InVision	
UI/UX Design	
Agile, Scrum	
Languages	

Languages

Ukrainian	••••
Russian	••••
English	••••
Finnish	••••

Interests

■ Sports, Travelling, Development and Cloud.

Recent Integrify graduate with a visual eye for web experiences, passion for building web and mobile apps working across the full-stack. I have completed several web apps from the ground up using React, Node, Typescript, and AWS. I am a hardworking and dedicated person, love for creativity, and always have a hunger to learn more.

Work experience

Full Stack Developer

Integrify, Helsinki

Sep 2020 - Jan 2021

React Native, JavaScript, Expo, Native Base, TypeScript, Redux, Contentful CMS and AWS

Teamwork project for a client of Integrity. Development of mobile application. Collaboration with 4 developers on a team. Usage Agile scrum methodology.

Junior Web Developer

Apr 2020 - May 2020

Integrify, Helsinki

CSS, React.js, Gatsby.js, JavaScript and Contentful CMS.

Teamwork project for a client of Integrity. Development of web application. Collaboration with 3 developers on a team.

Projects

ProBlog web application

Progressive Web Application... . Find more description in My Portfolio web app. Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Contentful CMS, Firebase, and PWA.

Task-manager API

A Representational State Transfer API Find more description in My Portfolio web app. Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, REST API, and Nodemailer/SendGrid

My cloud-storage

My Cloud Storage is a full-stack app... . Find more descriptions in My Portfolio web app. CSS, MaterializeCSS, JavaScript, React.js, Redux and AWS

My Portfolio

My Portfolio is animated, scrollable, and... . Find more descriptions in My Portfolio web app. *CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React.js and EmailJS*

Training Programs

Full Stack Development

May 2020 - Sep 2020

Integrify Academy, Helsinki

Learned stack: *Materialize CSS, NativeBase, React.js, React Native, JavaScript, Redux, TypeScript, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, GraphQL, REST API, Docker and AWS.*

Web Development

Nov 2019 - Apr 2020

Integrify Academy, Helsinki

Learned stack: HTML, CSS, SASS, BEM, Git, GitHub, JavaScript, React.js, Gatsby.js, Contentful, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, InVision, InVision Studio.

Education

Jurisprudence, Bachelor's degree

Sep 2011 - May 2013

"Interregional Academy of Personnel Management", Ukraine

Lawyer, Junior Specialist

Sep 2003 - May 2006

"Donbas State Technical University", College of Law, Ukraine